freescoreonline.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy

**OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY**

Last updated: 3/5/2010

We use the terms 'you' and 'your' to include any person who accesses the Sites or purchases the any product or service offered on the Sites (the 'Services') for any amount of time. We use the terms 'we', 'us' and 'our' to refer to One Technologies, L.P. (the 'Company'), which owns and/or operates this website, and our employees, members, officers, partners, affiliated entities, representatives, attorneys, and agents.

We understand how important your privacy is to you, so we are committed to assuring your privacy. This page outlines all of the steps we take to protect your privacy and what we do with your information that you provide to us through our web site.

**Protecting your information**

We use SSL-encryption technology when transferring and receiving consumer data on our and our affiliates' websites to protect your personal information. We have partnered with VeriSign or other equally reliable encryption services to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. However, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. We make no warranty, express, implied, or otherwise, that we will prevent unauthorized access to your private information.

**What information do we collect?**

In order to provide you with our services, we collect two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

**Personally Identifiable Information:** This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering for a membership, ordering a product or service, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), email address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, assets, liabilities, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the product or service, if you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to obtain the product or service you want. You should be aware that if you enter any personal information during the information request process and then hit the 'continue' or any other button on that page, the information you have entered will be transmitted to us, even though you may not complete the process on subsequent pages.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet.

**How do we use information we collect?**

We will use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our site, fill orders, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze site use, improve our product and service offerings, and customize our site's content, layout, and services. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Site Terms of Use, Sales Terms and Conditions, and this Private Policy. Your information may also be used by us or by third parties to whom we transfer it to provide the products or services you have requested.

When you use our site we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly in that case.

We may use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they will place a separate cookie on your computer. We and our third party ad server may collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular ad.

**With whom do we share your information?**

We may sell, trade, rent or otherwise transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to others. We provide the products and services offered on our website through contractual arrangements with affiliates, service providers, and other third parties. We and such third parties use your Personally Identifiable Information to operate our sites and to deliver their products and services. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products and services purchased on this site; release your Personally Identifiable Information to the third party that will provide the products or services that you ordered; and provide order information to third parties that help us provide customer service. We will encourage our service providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our service providers is governed by the privacy policies of those service providers, and is not subject to our control.

We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

We also allow some of our employees and independent contractors access to both Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information to enable us to assist us with our business and provide the services and products that we offer to you. We endeavor to have all such employees and contractors sign non-disclosure or confidentiality agreements with us in order to protect your information. From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who provide them to us available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive mailings from other reputable companies.

**Privacy Policies of Third Parties**

When you sign-up for services through our site, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policies. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses our use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site, and companies to whom your information is transferred, have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. You should also be aware that unsubscribing from us will not automatically unsubscribe you from third parties.

**Updating your account information**

Corrections or updates to your account information, including your email address, mailing address or credit card information can be made through the 'Account Info' section of your FreeScoreOnline.com; account. If necessary, other corrections or updates to your information can be made by contacting a customer care representative at 855-367-4817.

**Business transitions**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, customer information (both Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information) may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired, such customer information will be included within the transferred assets.

**Opting out**

If you no longer wish to receive our emails, newsletter or promotional offers, you may "opt-out" of receiving these communications by opting-out on our unsubscribe page or by clicking here to [unsubscribe.](http://www.optout-jnjw.net/o-jnjw-v08-c0737ff57739080e35f0817fbb38ac21)

**Changes to our policy**

We may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it frequently. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our Site Terms & Conditions, and by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to maintain a valid email address as a registered user, review this site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. Your use of the site after such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy.

**Miscellaneous/Contact Information**

You must be at least 18 years old to use this site. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors who are under 18 years of age.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

FreeScoreOnline.com;  
Attn: Customer Care  
4447 North Central Expressway, Suite 110, PMB 406  
Dallas, TX 75205

**The FreeScoreOnline.com; team is available to answer your questions via phone seven days a week.**  
Live representatives are available at 855-367-4817 during the following hours:

Monday through Friday, 8AM to 8PM CST  
Saturday, 8AM to 5PM CST  
Sunday, 12PM to 6PM CST

**Other Internet Privacy Resources**

We invite you to learn more about your privacy rights on the Internet. The following resources provide an array of information and services you might find helpful and informative. Electronic Privacy and Information Center (EPIC) EPIC is a public interest research center in Washington, DC. Established in 1994, EPIC works in association with Privacy International, an international human rights group based in London, and is a member of the Global Internet Liberty Campaign and the Internet Privacy Coalition. The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) The Federal Trade Commission enforces a variety of federal antitrust and consumer protection laws. The commission works to enhance the smooth operation of the marketplace by eliminating acts or practices that are unfair or deceptive. National Fraud Information Center (NFIC) The National Fraud Information Center is a project of the National Consumers League, America's oldest nonprofit consumer organization. NFIC helps consumers report fraud and offers advice on how to avoid being victimized. The Privacy Rights Clearinghouse (PRC) PRC provides consumers with valuable information on protecting their personal privacy.

RETURN TO TOP

Copyright © 2016 FreeScoreOnline.com;. All Rights Reserved.
